Abigail Silin Willing to relocate

Discord asilin#9769 linkedin.com/in/asilinphoto

PROFICIENCIES

- GitHub
- Salesforce
- Zendesk
- Smartsheet
- Monday.com
- Airtable
- Microsoft Office Suite (Excel)
- Google Workplace (Sheets)
- Notion
- Discord
- Slack
- Async communication

WORKING KNOWLEDGE

- JavaScript
- Adobe Suite
- General Blockchain knowledge

SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Communication
- Collaboration
- Data analysis
- Detail-oriented
- Grant coordination
- Innovation
- Onboarding
- Problem-solving
- Process development, implementation, and optimization
- Project coordination
- Project management
- Research administration
- Team building
- Tracking metrics
- Training

ABOUT ME

I'm a Coordinator located in Vermont, USA, with a passion for art, communication, project management, and the world of Web3. I have experience working with various stakeholders, liaising amongst teams, analyzing, optimizing processes, and working with researchers. I'm intrinsically motivated to succeed, provide the best possible experience for those I'm working with, and am a natural leader and collaborator.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts • Art, Communication, and the Environment

Green Mountain College • Poultney, VT • 2009 - 2013

EMPLOYMENT

Research Administrator • Protocol Labs • Remote • 2022 - 2023

- Designed initiatives supporting and improving the research-to-implementation pipeline across the company
- Supported goals of research-development labs across competing timelines
- Managed logistics of research collaborations across the globe
- Built and maintained relationships with collaborating labs and institutions
- Coordinated and improved coordination with internal stakeholders across the Marketing, Research, Legal, and Finance teams
- Oversaw and broadcast grants program
- Recruited speakers for and hosted Research Seminar series
- Edited and maintained PL Research website
- Temporarily managed marketing initiatives including overseeing Twitter, posting YouTube content, and writing newsletters
- Led and promoted company-wide learning initiatives

Research Operations Administrator • Curebase • Remote • 2022 - 2023

- Created and led onboarding of teammates within department
- Gathered and visualized performance metrics
- Led project forecasting and resource tracking
- Facilitated internal trainings
- Identified process gaps, improved and implemented processes
- Developed and maintained process and training documents
- Led and oversaw inter-departmental initiatives
- Maintained document organization and standardization

Immersion Operations Specialist* - Facebook (via The Mom Project) - Remote - 2020 - *Contract

- Partnered with Product Managers and Customer Immersion for upcoming research studies
- Screened, recruited, scheduled, and interacted with clients for upcoming studies
- Assisted with creation of recruiting surveys as needed
- Monitored processes and analyze for [potential future] scalability

UX Research Recruiting Coordinator* - Google (via Infosys) - Austin, TX - 2020 - *Contract

- Partnered and collaborated with UX Researchers
- Edited screener surveys for individual studies
- Searched for, screened, recruited, and interacted with research participants
- Monitored and documented participant activity
- Coordinated with reception to welcome and direct on-site participants
- Updated calendars, timelines, and managed details and logistics for multiple UX studies simultaneously

Abigail Silin Willing to relocate

Discord asilin#9769 linkedin.com/in/asilinphoto

CERTIFICATIONS

- CAPM Certification
- Google Analytics IQ
- Advanced Google Analytics

CURRENT COURSES

As of Feb. 25

- JavaScript Fundamentals by Alchemy University
- Become a Blockchain Developer learning path by LinkedIn
- Learn Git & GitHub by Codecademy

Reporting Analyst* • Indeed (via Experis) • Austin, TX • 2020 • *Contract

- Communicated with CSI specialists about sales requests
- Pulled data and presented decks for Sales to share with clients
- Provided metrics reporting in various formats for various levels of comprehension

Operations Coordinator & Hire Help* - Indeed (via Staffmark) - Austin, TX - 2018 - 2019 - *Contract

- Liaised between Sales and Hire teams for conflict resolution
- Pinpointed and troubleshot product issues to optimize work flow
- Answered questions related to Hire product sales, client onboarding, client accounts, and sales commission credit
- Prepared, edited, and posted client's job descriptions on Indeed.com
- · Assigned recruiters to accounts based on continually evolving data sets
- Provided weekly reports of recruiting goals and progress
- · Created and maintained training documents
- Trained co-workers

Project Coordinator • Trio Electric • Austin, TX • 2018

- · Assisted Project Managers and Foremen with projects
- Logged and maintained drawings, submittals, and information requests to and from Architectural Engineers
- Scheduled permits and inspections with the city of Austin
- Tracked and maintained project schedules
- Pulled reports for Project Managers and Finance

News Assistant & Podcast Producer - Burlington Free Press (Gannett) - Burlington, VT - 2017 - 2018

- Customer service
- Managed social media accounts
- · Provided and analyzed monthly social media engagement statistics
- Recorded, edited, produced, released, and cross-promoted podcast
- Maintained archives
- Published content on digital and print platforms
 Assisted with travel and mileage of newsroom employees

Account Coordinator • Burlington Free Press (Gannett) • Burlington, VT • 2016 - 2017

- Communicated needs of clients to design team to build advertising campaigns (digital and print)
- Client support
- Scheduling, reporting, and data entry for advertisements
- Coordinated and executed monthly and quarterly publications
- · Trained co-workers and sales team on new programs
- Assisted with new employee onboarding